Commerce Minister Tofal Ahmed has said that risk insurance will be introduced
for workers in the ready-made garment sector very soon.
He said this at a contract signing ceremony organized for the Dhaka Reporters Unity Parliament on the occasion of group insurance today.  Dhaka
Reporters Unity President Shakhat Hossain
Badsha presided over the event, while General Secretary Elias
Hossain and
Managing Director of Sunlife Insurance Company Limited M
Solaiman Hossain delivered speeches.
The Commerce Minister said that the market price for the upcoming Eid will be
within the purchasing power of buyers.   The
market will
remain within the purchasing power of the people during this Eid as well.  Those who
once served Bangladesh with bottomless
baskets are now calling it a miracle that Bangladesh has
emerged as a global powerhouse.  Our
Honorable Prime Minister
set the goal during the election period that
Bangladesh would become a Digital Bangladesh and a
country of middle class by 21 years.  Digital
Bangladesh is no longer a dream today, it is a reality.